// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "How shall the summer arise in joy, Or the summer fruits appear if _____.",
    answer: "All of the Above",
    options: [
          "Buds are nipped",
          "Blossoms are blown",
          "Plants are stripped",
          "All of the Above"
    ]
  },
   
   {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who does he compare himself to when he says “How can a child when fears annoy, But droop his tender wing, And forget his youthful spring.?",
    answer: "Caged bird",
    options: [
       "Book",
       "Flower",
       "Nip in the",
       "Caged bird"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The little ones spend the day, in _____ and _____ ?",
    answer: "Sighing, dismay",
    options: [
          "Sighing, dismay",
          "Happiness, glory",
          "Happiness, joy",
          "Sighing, sorrow"
    ]
  },
    
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who sings along with the school boy?",
    answer: "Skylark",
    options: [
         "His parents",
         "Huntsman",
         "Skylark",
         "His friends"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "I _____ to rise on a sunday morn?",
    answer: "Love",
    options: [
          "Hate",
          "Despise",
          "Regret",      
          "Love"
    ]
  },

       {
       numb: 6,
       question: "Who is he talking to when he says “if buds are nip’d ?",
       answer: "His parents",
       options: [
       "His parents",
       "Teacher",
       "Caged bird",
       "All of the Above"
     ]
   },
     
      {
       numb: 7,
       question: "Nor in my _____ can I take delight",
       answer: "Book",
       options: [
       "Book",
       "Learning bower",
       "Dreary shower",
       "All of the Above"
     ]
   },

      {
       numb: 8,
       question: "What drives all the joy away?",
       answer: "School on a summer morning",
       options: [
        "Caged bird",
        "Nip in the bud",
        "Blown blossoms",
        "School on a summer morning"
     ]
   },
     
     {
       numb: 9,
       question: "What does the boy like about the huntsman?",
       answer: "Sound of his horn",
       options: [
           "Sound of his horn",
           "Hunting skills",
           "His personality",
           "All of the Above"
     ]
   },
    
     {
       numb: 10,
       question: "Who is the poet of the poem “The School Boy?",
       answer: "William Blake",
       options: [
           "William Blake",
           "Thomas Wilde",
           "Rabindranath Tagore",
           "T.S. Eliot"
     ]
   },
    
    

 ];